{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523134492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523134492"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" d23d5d74-49c1-4495-ad31-bb880f4fa883"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwangu_wazi-sisi-mwangu-gari"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mwangu"," userResponse":" mwangu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523169413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523169412"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" d23d5d74-49c1-4495-ad31-bb880f4fa883"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zaidi_pia-zaidi-ndege-katika"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" zaidi"," userResponse":" zaidi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523213063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523213062"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" d23d5d74-49c1-4495-ad31-bb880f4fa883"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtini_mwili-sisi-uchungu-mtini"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mtini"," userResponse":" mtini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523275437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523275433"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" d23d5d74-49c1-4495-ad31-bb880f4fa883"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mtini_mwili-sisi-uchungu-mtini"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523275576","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523275576"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" d23d5d74-49c1-4495-ad31-bb880f4fa883"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523295775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523295775"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 227cdf6b-85f2-490d-9a04-85be4aab80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523295999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523295999"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 227cdf6b-85f2-490d-9a04-85be4aab80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523296962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523296962"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 227cdf6b-85f2-490d-9a04-85be4aab80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523298235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523298235"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 227cdf6b-85f2-490d-9a04-85be4aab80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523301156","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523301156"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 227cdf6b-85f2-490d-9a04-85be4aab80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523301999","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523301999"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 227cdf6b-85f2-490d-9a04-85be4aab80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523302312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523302311"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 227cdf6b-85f2-490d-9a04-85be4aab80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523302438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523302438"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 227cdf6b-85f2-490d-9a04-85be4aab80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_12"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523302517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523302517"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 227cdf6b-85f2-490d-9a04-85be4aab80c7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523313959","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523313958"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" LAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523321635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523321635"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523323228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523323227"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" LAINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523328160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523328160"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LAINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523329739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523329739"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" LALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523333368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523333367"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LALA"," userResponse":" LALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523335009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523335008"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" LIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523340201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523340200"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" START_LIMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523343425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523343424"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523345019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523345019"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMAU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" LIMAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523350066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523350065"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LIMAU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIMAU"," userResponse":" LIMAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523351711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523351710"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523359131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523359130"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-L.rand.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523361169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523361168"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548523361263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548523361262"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 2498b5a9-e6ce-47e2-a07b-538198c1e8ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-L.rand.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" LORI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524736905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524736905"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 87d31b74-2cf6-40bb-9183-555591d80401"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548524738741","data":{"timestamp":" 1548524738741"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190126_201807"," gameId":" 87d31b74-2cf6-40bb-9183-555591d80401"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}